迈克 · 诺斯: 所以这个命令会变得有点模糊和麻烦。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So this commands are gonna
get kind of vague and cumbersome.
传统的方法是使用配置文件来代替。
The conventional way to do this is
to use a configuration file instead.
所以在我的源文件夹中，我要创建一个文件站点。
So in my source folder,
I'm gonna create a file site.
在 hello-ts 文件夹中，我将创建一个名为 tsconfig.json 的文件。
In the hello-ts folder, I'm gonna
create a file called tsconfig.json.
迈克 · 诺斯: 我们来看看你可以在这里做的各种事情
&gt;&gt; Mike North: And we're gonna look at
the various things you can do here to
安排一下。
set it up.
在配置编译器时需要考虑两件事。
There are two things you need to think
about when configuring the compiler.
第一步是定义哪些文件是输入。
Number one is defining
which files are the inputs.
您可以通过指定一个文件列表，或者
And you can do that either by
specifying a list of files, or
我的偏好是 include，它可以让你指定一些全局变量。
my preference is include,
which lets you specify some globs.
你以前见过像 star.ts 之类的 globs。
You seen globs before like star.ts or
something.
一个有效的 glob 是源文件夹中的所有内容。
One valid glob is everything
in source folder.
对，这就是第一点。
Right, so that's number one.
我们在编译什么？
What are we compiling?
第二个选择是，我们如何编译它？
The second option is,
how are we compiling it?
有哪些编译器选项？
What are the compiler options?
所以为了得到和我们刚才看到的一样的结果,
So to get an equivalent result
of what we were just looking at,
我们会做一个模块 commonjs，目标。
we would do module commonjs, target.
Vs Code 提供了一些，这个文件背后有一个 JSON 模式
And VS Code gives you some,
there's a JSON schema behind this file
它会给出这个的允许值。
that'll give you the allowed values for
this.
所以我们选择 es2017
So we'll pick es2017, and
只是为了好玩，我实际上要把输出到一个不同的目录。
just for fun I'm actually gonna put
the output in a different directory.
把它放到 lib 文件夹中。
Put it in the lib folder.
这使得只发布编译后的输出变得非常容易。
And this would make it really easy to sort
of to publish only the compiled output.
如果这是一个图书馆，我会把它发布到 npm
If this were a library,
I'd wanna publish that to npm so
和 TypeScript 消费者一样，可以导入我的代码。
that JavaScript and TypeScript
consumers alike, can import my code.
他们不需要能够读取这些文件。
They don't have to be
able to read ts files.
所以现在我可以运行 tsc。
So now I can just run tsc.
一切看起来都很好，我应该，在这里刷新之后,
Everything looks good, and
I should, after refreshing here,
有一个包含这个 index.js 的 lib 文件夹。
have a lib folder with
this index.js in it.
这真是太棒了。
So this is great.
所以我几乎可以认为，如果我删除我们在这里的第一次尝试。
So I could almost think of it as,
if I delete our first attempt here.
我可以把我们想象成我们的源文件夹有一个 ts 文件,
I could think of us,
like our source folder has a ts file,
我们的 lib 文件夹有 js 输出。
our lib folder has the js output.
我可以检查源文件夹到 Git，我只能发布库文件夹,
I could check the source folder into Git,
and I could only publish the lib folder,
因为我们只关心编译后的输出。
because we really only care
about the compiled output.
这样你就能把事情组织得井井有条。
And you'd keep things very
well organized in that way.
这真是太棒了。
So this is great.
不过我发现了一个问题，我们有这么多优秀的类型信息
One problem I see though, we have
all this great type information and
我要求用户运行的东西缺少这种类型的信息。
the stuff that I would ask my users to
run is missing this type information.
现在，我有必要提供一个不使用 type 的选项
Now, it's necessary for
me to provide an option to not use type
因为人们可能会编写依赖于这些代码的 JavaScript 应用程序。
information because people might write
JavaScript apps that depend on this code.
但是我想确保我提供了一些其他的东西在那之上。
But I wanna make sure I provide
some other stuff on top of that.
所以我们要说声明为真，SourceMap 为真。
So we're gonna say declaration true and
SourceMap true.
再次运行编译器，我们会看到在 lib 文件夹中弹出一些新文件。
Run the compiler again and we should see
some new files pop up in the lib folder.
其中一个是.d.ts 文件，对吗？
One of them is a .d.ts file, right?
同样的文件名，但是它是. d.ts 而不是. js。
Same file name but
it's .d.ts instead of .js.
这个，如果你看它，它看起来有点像一个没有实现的函数,
And this, if you look at it, it looks kind
of like a function with no implementation,
我们可以看到我论点的名字都在这里。
we can see that the names
of my arguments are there.
我们可以看到我们有参数的类型。
We can see that we have types for
the arguments.
这个我们马上就会知道，但是
This, we'll learn in a moment, but
这恰好是你表示函数返回类型的方式。
it happens to be the way you represent
the return type of the function.
但是这里没有任何东西能够描述如何将 a 和 b 加在一起。
But nothing in here describes how you
would actually add a and b together.
没有什么可以描述我们在返回之前等待了半秒钟。
And nothing describes that we're waiting
half a second before returning that.
所以这是一个类型声明文件
So this is a type declaration
file that is meant
在 JavaScript 的顶部添加一个层，它表示。
to layer right on top of the JavaScript,
that it represents.
如果你使用的是一个支持打字脚本的编辑器，比如 VS 代码,
And if you're using a TypeScript
aware editor, like VS Code,
它会读取这个，然后把它和 JavaScript 匹配
it's going to read this and
kind of match it with that JavaScript and
理解这些类型是为了配合这段代码,
understand that these are the types that
are meant to go along with this code,
这是为了得到我们想要的价值而运行的。
which is what is run in order
to get the value we're after.
另一个文件是源映射，对吗？
The other file is a source map, right?
所以这就是让我们,
So, this is what would let us,
如果在代码中加入断点，在调试器中,
if you put break points in your code,
it's what would, in your debugger,
将断点映射回原始打字稿源。
map that break point back to
the original TypeScript source.
所以你有点像是在通过打字稿代码进行调试,
So you kind of feel as if you're
debugging through TypeScript code,
但事实上，这不是逃跑的原因。
when in fact, that is not what's running.
正在运行的是 JavaScript。
What's running is the JavaScript.
我可以通过在这里给你另一个配置示例来结束。
I can close by giving you
another example config here.
所以这是一个更复杂的问题。
So this is a more complicated one.
编译器具有对反应的本机支持。
The compiler has native support for react.
所以它可以通过 JSX。
So it can pass JSX.
可以理解，如果你调用你的文件 TSX，这就像一个打字稿的反应文件。
Can understand that if you call your files
TSX, that's like a TypeScript react file.
但是你不需要任何东西，除了打字稿
But you don't need anything
other than the TypeScript
编译器来检查。
compiler in order to check that.
严格，设置严格的真实是非常重要的。
Strict, setting strict to
true is really important.
你可能想要严格为假，这是默认的
You may wanna have strict as false,
it's default
从 JavaScript 转移到 TypeScript。
as your sort of Moving from
JavaScript to TypeScript.
我将向您展示的方法包括从松散的配置和
The approach I'll show you involves
starting with the loose configuration and
然后拧紧。
then tightening it up.
但是最终，你想要在一个地方结束你的生命
But ultimately,
you wanna end up in a place where you've
开启了一些严格的功能。
got some of these strict
features turned on.
禁止任何暗示，这也很重要。
Forbidding implicit any,
that's also important.
隐含的茴香就像是百搭牌。
Implicit anys are like wild card.
它们是编译器无法自己解决问题的地方。
They're places where the compiler
couldn't figure things out by itself.
这是一个允许任何类型的地方。
And it's kind of a place
where any type is allowed.
说得更悲观一点,
And to put that in a more pessimistic way,
那是个没有字体安全的地方，对吗？
it's a place where you have
no type safety, right?
编译器可以检查和编译常规的 JavaScript。
The TypeScript compiler can check and
compile regular JavaScript.
如果你有兴趣了解更多,
And if you are interested in
learning more about this,
查看 Visual Studio Code 的 FrontEnd Masters 课程。
check out the Visual Studio Code
course on FrontEnd Masters.
您可以使用 JSdoc 注释并声明这个函数有一个参数和
You can use JSdoc comments and
say that this function has an argument and
它是字符串类型，这里是描述和
it is of type string and
here is the description and
编译器实际上会将其作为类型信息读取。
the compiler will actually
read that as type information.
所以即使你处在一个你不能切换的位置
So even if you are in a position
where you can't actually switch
文件，你仍然可以使用打字稿编译器来检查和
to TS files, you can still use
the TypeScript compiler to check and
确保你的代码以一种类型安全的方式排列。
make sure that your code kind
of lines up in a type-safe way.
我们已经讨论了目标环境，他们经常添加
And we already talked about the target
environment, and they regularly add
并且与 JavaScript 规范的新草案保持同步。
features, and keep pace with new drafts
of the JavaScript specification.
所以 async 和 await 是最近添加的。
So async and await were things
that were added recently.
我希望他们能对一些新的东西，项目领域做些什么。
I expect they will do something about
some of the new stuff, project fields.
在官方 JavaScript 规范中添加内容时,
As things are added to
the official JavaScript spec,
你会看到他们成为新的目标。
you'll see them added as a new target.
迈克 · 诺斯: 什么事？
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Yes?
演讲者2: 如果你想支持，你有什么建议吗,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Do you have a recommendation
for if you wanted to support,
我记得你说过 ES3就像 IA6。
say, I think you said ES3 was like IA6.
迈克 · 诺斯: 是的 演讲者2: 如果你想得到支持
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Yep.
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: If you wanted the support to
比如 IE 或者其他所有的，或者你根本不想支持 IE,
say like IE or all them, or
you didn't want to support IE at all,
除非他们的目标。
unless their targets.
迈克 · 诺斯: 是的，问得好。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Yep, good quesiton there.
所以说真的，我能要求你们改进你们的问题吗？
So really, can I ask you to
refine your question there?
你在考虑把巴别塔用在打字稿上吗？
Are you thinking about using
Babel with typescript?
讲者2: 是的 迈克 · 诺斯: 所以,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yes.
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So that,
使用 Babel 和打字脚本，可以将打字脚本减少到真正的
using Babel with TypeScript that
would reduce TypeScript to really
只是检查器，而不是产生输出的东西。
just the checker,
not the thing it's producing the output.
我建议设置的方式是让打字脚本发出非常,
And the way I would recommend setting that
up, would be have TypeScript emit very,
非常非常现代的 JavaScript，让 Babel 来完成剩下的工作。
very, very modern JavaScript, and
let Babel take it the rest of the way.
你已经有了一些可以接受常规 JavaScript 和
You already have something that
can take regular JavaScript and
像使用巴别塔预置，你可以只列出你的浏览器，对不对？
target like with using Babel preset and
you can just list your browsers, right?
然后说，我关心最后两个版本的 Chrome。
And say, I care about the last
two versions of Chrome.
而且这个库实际上与 Chrome 保持同步，并且
And that library actually keeps
up to date with Chrome, and
基本上可以免除你的责任
will basically remove that
responsibility from you and
你的团队在跟踪什么功能我应该启用和什么不？
your team in terms of keeping track of
what feature should I enable and what not?
所以我会说，让你的目标成为 ESNext。
So I would say,
leave your target as ESNext maybe.
现在随着项目变得越来越大,
Now, as projects get really big,
有时候有些语言特征并不吸引人。
sometimes there are language features
that just are not appealing to include.
例如，在 LinkedIn 我们有一个支持异步的应用程序
For example, at LinkedIn we
have an app that enabling async
等待是很困难的，因为每一次等待
in await would be tough,
just because at every await
我们得用蓄热器之类的东西来填充。
we have to polyfill using regenerator or
something like that.
这开始变得昂贵,
And this starts to get expensive,
这实际上大大增加了资产规模。
it actually increases
the asset size quite a bit.
所以我会把所有这些都留给借贷工具和巴别塔。
So I would leave all of that in
the hands of lending tools and Babel.
如果你只是使用编译器作为静态分析工具,
And if you're just using the compiler
as a static analysis tool, well,
把你的目标设置在 ESNext。
leave your target set at ESNext.